Djonathan Krause

Blumenau, Santa Catarina, Brazil



odjonathankrause@gmail.com



+55 47 99155-4827



linkedin.com/in/djonathan-krause-8981a788

Summary

Experience developing within the HighJump/Körber platform utilizing Advantage Architect, WebWise Page Editor. Proficient with relational database development using SQL Server/Oracle.

History working in big projects leading teams and performing code reviews, technical guidance to other developers, and designing process flows (technical/functional).

Experience



Software Developer

Körber Supply Chain LATAM

Jan 2020 - Apr 2022 (2 years 4 months)

- Lead the development team in the largest WMS project in Latin America (2019/2022) with a team of multiple developers;
- Manage projects keeping the customer up to date on the project;
- Code and test using mainly SQL, Architect, and WebWise Page Editor;
- Go-live at customers' site;
- Define WMS functionally and technically;
- Help to develop new tools;
- Help to improve methodology and coding standards;
- Training new co-workers;



Software Developer

Otimis - Körber

Feb 2019 - Apr 2022 (3 years 3 months)



🔭 Software Developer

LINCROS

Aug 2018 - Oct 2018 (3 months) Java Full Stack Developer



Software Developer

Körber Supply Chain Mar 2018 - Aug 2018 (6 months)



Support Analyst

Körber Supply Chain

Feb 2017 - Mar 2018 (1 year 2 months)

Working as a Support Analyst I develop bug fixes and tests and analyze new potential errors in the WMS system from reputed companies like AmBev, Renner, Martins, Drogaria Araújo, Wine...

In this position I have to use my skills on Oracle SQL, Microsoft SQL Server and system development to find and fix bugs.

em Technical Support

Körber Supply Chain

Oct 2015 - Feb 2017 (1 year 5 months)

Working as a Support Technician I help users about doubts and errors in processes of WMS system of renowned companies like AmBev, Renner, Martins, Drogaria Araújo, Wine...

estágio

Körber Supply Chain Jul 2015 - Oct 2015 (4 months)

IT Technician

SENAI/SC - Serviço Nacional de Aprendizagem Industrial Dec 2014 - Jun 2015 (7 months)

Education

FURB - Universidade de Blumenau

Bachelor's degree, Computer Science 2014 - 2018

Licenses & Certifications

Duolingo English Fluency: Advanced (Estimated) - Duolingo

II HIGHJUMP UNIVERSITY

Minicurso Básico de Power BI - DATAB 001769

Skills

SQL • Oracle • English • Software Development • Computer Science • Programming • Analytical Skills • Supply Chain Management • PL/SQL • JAVA